const flashcardData2 = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Everyone should keep their ______ frozen at all times.",
    "answer": "credit reports",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Missed payments hurt you for ___ years. ",
    "answer": "7",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "You should have __ to __ months in a High Yield Savings Account.",
    "answer": "3, 6",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "____ is preferred over ____ because it has better legal protection and a backdoor stratgey.",
    "answer": "401(k); Roth IRA",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The 3 types of mutual funds are ____, ____, and ____.",
    "answer": "open-end mutual funds, exchange-traded funds, closed-end funds",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "You should focus on ____, ____, and ____ when you buy a mutual fund.",
    "answer": "diversification, fees, asset allocation",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "When you get a job, you should immediately __ __ for employer's _____ plan.",
    "answer": "sign up; 401(k)",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Never try to ____ the market. It doesn't really work.",
    "answer": "time",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The 2 primary models of advisor fees are ____ and ____ model.",
    "answer": "AUM; hourly",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "You should keep your average expense ratio ____ ___ percent.",
    "answer": "below; 0.25",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "You should invest in ___ ___ or ___. Choose low-cost ___ ___.",
    "answer": "Mutual Funds; ETFs; index funds",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Don't fill up yout ___ early because of the lack of _____ feature.",
    "answer": "401(k); \"true-up\"",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "When saving for retirement, one should tyipcally invest in their _______ accounts before investing in their _____ account.",
    "answer": "tax-advantaged (IRA & 401(k)); brokerage",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Always pay your ______ Balance by the ___ ___.",
    "answer": "Statement; due date",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "___ ___ are used in 90% of lending decisions. They help lenders evaulate your ability and likeliness to repay on time.",
    "answer": "FICO Score",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "You ___ money for bonds and you ____ stock in a company for stocks.",
    "answer": "lend; own",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "____ are generally less volatile than ___.",
    "answer": "bonds; stocks",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Most target date funds ____ their allocations to ____ over time.",
    "answer": "decrease; stocks",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "If a company files for bankruptcy, the company's ____ is most at risk of becoming virtually worthless.",
    "answer": "stock",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "A good strategy for saving for retirement is to set up ____ ____ to your retirement savings account.",
    "answer": "automatic contributions",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "In the book \"All Your Worth,\" Elizabeth Warren and Amelia Warren Tyagi reccommend that you budget no ___ than __% of after-tax income for expense that you must pay every month.",
    "answer": "more; 50",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "A company's board of directors may choose to pay _____ to shareholders, providing them with a portion of the company's profits.",
    "answer": "dividends",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "____ ______ occurs when the market price of a stock increases, contributing to the investor's total return along with dividends.",
    "answer": "Capital appreciation",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Active mutual funds aim to ____ the market, while passive index funds aim to ____ the market.",
    "answer": "beat; match",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "Index funds trade once per day at the end of the trading day but ETFs trade _____ throughout the trading day.",
    "answer": "intra-day",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "An ETF is a basket of securities that trades on an exchange and typically has ____ fees compared to actively managed mutual funds.",
    "answer": "lower",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Over time, many passive index funds have been shown to _____ the average active investors.",
    "answer": "outperform",
    "type": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "The main goal of a passive index fund is to match a specific _____, rather than trying to outperform it.",
    "answer": "benchmark (index)",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "ETFs are often considered more ______ than index mutual funds due to how they are structured and traded.",
    "answer": "tax-efficient",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Rent is considered a ____ expense while dining out is considered a ____ expense.",
    "answer": "fixed; variable",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "HYS accounts ____ suffer a loss of principal because these accounts are insured by the ____.",
    "answer": "cannot; FDIC",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "An ____ ____ is not directly deducted on your statement; instead, it is taken out of the fund's ____ before you see your returns.",
    "answer": "expense ratio; earnings (or dividends)",
    "type": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "___ are commissions typically charged when you buy a mutual fund, and theyâ€™re shared by the mutual fund company with the advisor who sold you the fund.",
    "answer": "Loads",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Create financial goals using the SMART method. SMART stands for ___, ___, ___, ___, and ____.",
    "answer": "specific, measurable, relevant, time-bound",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "Some strategies to increase savings rate include putting savings on _____  or save half/spend half approach.",
    "answer": "auto-pilot",
    "type": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Never use a ____ ____ if you can't pay if off in full each month. No amount of points or miles is worth it.",
    "answer": "credit card",
    "type": "easy"
  }
]

export default flashcardData2;